https://www.servu-online.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Brand
Refrigeration
View All Refrigeration Refrigerators & FreezersReach-InsUndercounterWorktopChef BasesChest FreezersWalk-InsMerchandisersSwing Door CoolerSlide Door CoolerFreezerOpen Air CurtainFood Prep TablesPizza Preparation TablesSalad Sandwich TablesDeli CasesIce CreamBarBottle CoolersBack Bar CoolersDraft Beer DispensersGlass ChillersIce MachinesCuber Heads & BinsUndercountersHardware & AccessoriesRefrigeration ClearanceBar Equipment & Supplies
View All Bar Equipment & Supplies Bar RefrigerationBottle CoolersBack Bar CoolersDraft Beer DispensersGlass ChillersBeer EquipmentUnderbar UnitsSinks & DrainboardsWorkstation/Cocktail UnitsModular UnitsIce BinsLiquor DisplaysGlass Storage RacksFaucet/AccessoriesSpeedrailsPortable Bars & Beer MerchandisersGlass Washers & ChemicalsLiquor Pourers & StorageLiquor PourersLiquor StorageMatting & Sink AccessoriesWine Service & TubsDrink Prep SuppliesBlendersGlassware & DrinkwareGlasswarePlastic & Disposable DrinkwareFixturesGlass RacksService RailsBar RailingBar SecurityBar Equipment & Supplies ClearanceFurniture
View All Furniture Wood Frame SeatingChairsStoolsMetal Frame SeatingChairsStoolsTraditional Bar StoolsBucket Bar StoolsBackless Bar StoolsOpen Back Bar StoolsTable TopsQuick Ship LaminateCustom LaminateSolid WoodTable BasesComplete TablesBoothsUpholsteredContourStack ChairsOutdoorMetal FrameResinHigh Chairs & Booster SeatsStore Counters, Display & ReceptaclesFurniture PartsTable Base PartsSwivelsBasesSeatsVinylGlidesFurniture ClearanceDining Room
View All Dining Room Tablecloths & SkirtsTable SkirtingTablecloths & NapkinsGlasswarePlastic DrinkwareFlatwareDinnerwareChinaMelamineCandle LampsBasketsTable ServiceShakersCreamers & SugarRamekin & Sauce CupsSqueeze Bottles & ServersTable OrganizersSkillets & PlattersMenus & DisplaysMenu CoversTabletop SignsClips & Table NumbersTraysGuest ChecksApronsCash RegistersSigns & DecorDecorative SignsWrite-On & Teller SignsOutdoor SignsIlluminated SignsExit SignsWater Stations & Ice BinsDispensersNapkinCups & LidStrawIce CreamPacket OrganizersDisposablesDisplay Cases & CoversChafers & BuffetwareSalad Service & DeliwareFood BarsBeverage & CateringBeverage DispenserCatering TransportCoffee
& Tea ServiceTea DispensersBrewers & UrnsEspresso & CappuccinoServers & AccessoriesCoat RackFixturesDining Room ClearanceFood Prep & Storage
View All Food Prep & Storage Food StorageStorage Bins & BoxesIngredient BinsDunnage & Can Racks Food Labels & WrappingShelvingWall ShelvesWire ShelvesPlastic ShelvingKeg & SecurityWork Tables & Equipment StandsFractional Food PansMetal - High TempPlastic - Low TempPots & PansFry PansSauce Pans & BraziersStock Pots & BoilersRoastingInset Pots & Bain MariesSheet Pans & Baking PansSheet PansBaking PansPan RacksBaking SuppliesBaking UtensilsBowlsMeasuringPizza SuppliesPansDough BoxesUtensilsPizza BagsPan Racks & WrappingCooking Utensils & ToolsSpoonsTongsDishersLadlesGrill & Prep ToolsStrainers & ColandersCutleryTurnersCutting BoardsKnife StorageKnife SharpenersKnivesApparelApronsApparel & ShoesGlovesHeat ProtectionCan OpenersThermometers & TimersScalesFood Prep EquipmentFood ProcessorsElectronic Prep MachinesManual Prep MachinesSlicersMixersBowl MixersStick MixersMixer AccessoriesFood Prep & Storage ClearanceSanitation & Warewashing
View All Sanitation & Warewashing Anti Fatigue MatsCartsWarewashing SuppliesGlass RacksDish RacksFlatware Racks & StorageBus BoxesDishwashersUpright DishwashersUndercounter DishwashersBooster HeatersDish TablesPre-Rinse & FaucetsPre-Rinse SprayersFaucetsReplacement PartsSinksScullery SinksGrease InterceptorsDisposalsHand SinksMoppingMop SinksMop BucketsMopsFloor CareVaccuumers & SweepersFloor BuffersBrooms & Dust MopsTraffic MatsJanitorial SuppliesRestroom Fixtures & SuppliesChanging TablesRestroom Partitions & FixturesHand DryersDispensers & ReceptaclesUrinal Blocks & MatsTrash ReceptaclesSmoking SuppliesReceptaclesAshtraysAir CleanersOffice Equipment & SuppliesSafesSecurityInsect ControlSanitation & Warewashing ClearanceCooking Equipment
View All Cooking Equipment ConcessionsPopcornHot Dog EquipmentCondiment CentersFood CookersToastersWarmersFood WarmersFood CookersRice CookersOverhead WarmersWarming DrawersHeat LampsHot Food MerchandisersPizza EquipmentHot Food TablesMicrowavesCountertop Cooking EquipmentCharbroilersGriddlesCombination UnitsHot PlatesFryersPanini GrillsFryersCounterFloorBaskets/AccessoriesOil FiltrationProofing & HoldingSteam EquipmentConvection OvensOutdoor GrillsCooking AccessoriesBrushesHosesCastersGriddle SuppliesTimersPartsRangesHoods & ExhaustsGrease HoodsCondensate HoodsExhaust FansFire SuppressionGrease FiltersEquipment StandsCooking Equipment Clearance
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Serv-U Restaurant Equipment & Supply uses and protects any information
that you give Serv-U Restaurant Equipment & Supply when you use this website.
Serv-U Restaurant Equipment & Supply is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Serv-U Restaurant Equipment & Supply may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
maryreale@servu-online.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
[profiler]Memory usage: real: 13631488, emalloc: 13248864Code ProfilerTimeCntEmallocRealMem
